We beg you!
Please keep her in this house!
Put her in your house.
That's impossible!
I can only think of the Ayase residence
that can take in someone like this!
We already got a cat, so why not?
Don't lump me together
with a nobody like that!
That thing doesn't even eat!
So what happened
to the male one anyway?
It went back to the chemistry room.
Huh?
"I can stay an anatomical model without
worries as long as Hana is okay," he said.
But in return, he's gonna
sneak outta school at night
and he'd like to see Hana then.
We have to rely on
your magnanimous heart, Auntie!
Please!
Sheesh. Anatomical models
getting in heat, huh?
Just be lovey-dovey without
bothering the neighbors.
Anyway, what about the ball?
Oh, about that...
It was just a Christmas ornament.
Crazy.
Kinda like when animals make
their butts glow when they're courting?
Then it can't be helped.
No, I'm not convinced at all.
We're gonna eat, so pull the table out.
Okarun, you'll eat too, right?
Oh, sure. I'd love to.
Man, what a pain.
Momo, you have
some amazing powers, huh?
I understand why Auntie
trusted you to do the exorcism!
And Okarun, too!
That transformation was wicked!
It was so badass!
I wish I had some kind of power, too.
Oh, well, um...
I'm getting the table out
so can you guys move?
Oh, let me help!
Thanks. Hold that end.
Roger that!
Come on!
You're just getting in my way!
Oh, Momo, hold on.
Got some lint.
Yeah. Thanks.
Gimme more thanks, yeah?
Just move, please.
I'll get outta the way after one more.
Then I'll never say it.
You're the one I fell in love with.
I won't let go of you no matter what!
If I don't do anything right here and now,
I'll regret it for the rest of my life!
Miss Ayase!
There's lint!
Got it. Sorry about that.
Thanks.
And what's wrong?
I decided that
I'm not going to hold back.
I'm going to fight adamantly.
Against what?
I'm looking at only you
Since the day I met you,
all the way to right now
I want to shout that I love you
Let's try to change tomorrow
Hey, morons. You're in the way.
Settle down!
You'll kick up dust all over the place!
Sorry, ma'am!
And Momo, you're gonna stay over
at Jiji's place this weekend
so you better have your
underwear and stuff ready.
Hey! Why would you
say stuff like that?
Miss Ayase? At Mr. Jiji's house? Why!?
What? I didn't tell you?
Jiji's house is cursed
and he wants it exorcised.
That's why he came to our place.
Miss Ayase, were you going
to go there all alone with Mr. Jiji!?
Of course not.
I was planning on asking you
to come along, Okarun.
I'd feel a bit uneasy doing it by myself.
Then let's hurry up and get it done!
Let's resolve it quickly and have
Mr. Jiji hurry on home!
Thank you! Woo!
What? What now?
Crap! School at night is super scary!
Isn't it bad to go in without permission?
It's fine. We're just gonna
play with a Ouija board.
I'll film it on video.
Huh? Hold on,
do you hear something?
Come on, stop that.
- No way. For real?
- What? No, scary!
You're in the way! Stand aside!
KAMIGOE CITY STATION
Wait for me, Hana!
I'm coming to see you right now!
Hana!
He's not here yet.
And it's four o'clock already.
It's fine. I'll wait here
with you until he shows up.
I'm sure he'll come.
It'll be okay.
Sorry for being late, Hana.
Taro.
I love you.
Crap. I fell asleep.
What? Hey!
If you're here, you should wake me up!
Thank you so much, Miss Momo!
You were waiting with her!
I had a lot happen tonight, but starting
tomorrow, I will make sure to come on time.
You're gonna come every day?
KEEP OUT
JIJI'S ROOM
Damn it, I can't sleep again tonight.
Because of him.
I'll pretend to take this,
EPISODE 12
LET'S GO
TO THE CURSED HOUSE
and then take this one!
Okarun, you really suck
at playing Old Maid!
You guys just have demented personalities!
Maybe you're naïve? Yeah, naïve!
A naïve Okarun? Priceless!
I won't play anymore!
Sheesh, that was just a joke.
We're kidding!
Okarun! I'll give you some candy!
So cheer up!
Wow, these are so nostalgic.
I love these!
I bought a ton so you should
eat some too, Momo!
By the way, I was really impressed that
the candy shop over there still exists!
That grandma running the shop
never changes!
She still did the, "Here you go.
Your change is 500,000 yen," bit.
I was so touched
like Creamy Mami, woo!
I hate having thoughts like this.
I get fed up
with my own shortcomings.
But I can't do anything about this feeling.
I have to take my mind off of it somehow.
I have to concentrate
on getting my nut back!
Nut... Nut... Nut...
Nut...
Nut, nut, nut, nut, nut...
Nut, nut, nut, nut, nut, nut...
Okarun, what's wrong?
My nut!
Okarun, you're thinking about
your nut too much.
No, that's not it! This is...
Hey, I've been wondering
for a while now.
Since when have dirty jokes
been the new thing?
Oh no, that's not it.
There's a lot of things going on.
Then I'll make
something else get popular.
Hip joint!
No. Dirty jokes are not in.
Vamo lá!
That's Kazu's thing.
Pathetic! You're so pathetic, Ken!
But at this rate,
my own heart won't last!
I must take initiative
in grasping Miss Ayase's interests.
I will now talk about tsuchinokos!
Whoa now!
Tsuchinoko? I wanna hear!
UMAs are not creatures of fantasy!
Actually, even gorillas were UMAs
until about a hundred years ago!
And I believe that a tsuchinoko will be
the next UMA to follow in the footsteps of gorillas!
SPECIAL FEATURE
THE TRUTH ABOUT THE TSUCHINOKO
BECOME POPULAR WITH
HIGH DIMENSIONAL POWERS
Oh yeah, our village has
a legend of a great serpent.
A shrine that's said to have 200 years
of history and worships a great snake.
It's called Tsuchinoko Shrine!
Wow!
Let's go to that shrine! I want to see
a giant tsuchinoko snake!
Sheesh, you're so hopeless.
Stay close to me at all times, okay?
Crap! The initiative!
A mummified kappa!
There's a shrine that worships that, too.
So shrines that worship UMAs
are not that uncommon.
How's that? I'll toss that UMA shrine legend
right back at ya!
GIANT MAN-EATING WORM
DEEP DIVE!!
WHERE SUBTERRANEANS GATHER!
Seriously? Isn't that totally wicked?
That means kappas exist!
Wait, hold on, then what about Nessie?
They have a photo and everything!
I personally think they exist!
Because I want to see them!
The photograph of Nessie
is called the Surgeon's Photograph.
They have since determined it to be a fake,
but I saw one recently with my own eyes!
Seriously? I wanna see one, too!
Huh? Come to think,
this is the first time
So they really do exist!
that I've talked this much to someone
other than Miss Ayase.
More like, I've never been able
to talk about stuff like this.
This is fun!
Okarun, you're amazing!
You know everything!
I totally respect you as a friend!
F-Friend.
Huh? We're not?
I'm totally shocked, and absorbed.
You're one of Momo's friends, right?
Then can you make me
one of your friends, too?
Sorry, I am an awkward fellow
after all.
I told you to not say that!
Huh? What's up? Why?
You don't have to know, Jiji!
Even Momo is leaving me out
of the loop, too!
Why isn't he more despicable?
If he's such a good guy,
then I...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
This is a hot springs district!
It's in relation to my dad's work...
Wasn't your dad a teacher or something?
He's doing research on volcanoes
at a nearby college.
And that's why we all moved here, too.
MANJU
HOT SPRINGS MANJU
A volcano? Is it okay?
Not gonna erupt or anything?
TARGET PRACTICE
AMUSEMENT CENTER
There are records that it erupted
about 200 years ago.
But it seems to have calmed down since.
I see.
Slurp-a-durp!
Are we gonna...
I don't wanna hear it.
Hurray!
Slurp-a-durp!
This way now!
How is it, Momo?
Do you see a weird aura or anything?
Just how much stamina do you have?
I don't see anything at all.
Like, it's totally ordinary.
For real?
All the spirit mediums said
it was totally bad news!
More like I want to get
some rest first. I'm thirsty.
Wait, you really can't see anything?
Really? For real?
Really, for real.
H-Hold on, Miss Ayase.
Okarun, hurry on over!
Oh, okay.
How is it, Miss Ayase?
Do you see any weird auras or something?
How is it?
The TV turned on by itself!
That was me.
Oh, that scared me!
Why did you suddenly turn on the TV?
Because I'm bored.
There's nothing here.
And that's it for us!
Back to the studio!
Huh? Are you doubting me?
That's not it.
When spirit mediums came by,
they said this place was bad news, right?
This is my prediction, but maybe
those ghosts are hiding right now.
It was like this
back with Turbo Granny, too.
When the spirit's power is weak,
it's hard for me to notice them.
So it's easy for them to go into hiding.
In other words...
This'll be a piece of cake, yeah?
How awesome!
Lady Momo! Allow me
to massage your shoulders!
Hey!
I have no objections.
Oh, I want to drink some juice.
A sweet one!
I will get some ready right away!
Touched... Shoulder...
Let's get some rest for now.
Okarun, you should sit too.
Spirits are gonna show up at night anyway,
so let's rest when we can.
Okay.
And so, I'm gonna head out
into the hot springs district!
Huh?
Did you just say there were no spirits
because you wanted to go to the hot springs?
That's not true! There really aren't any!
Anyway, please have fun with Jiji, okay?
Huh? You're really gonna go?
What are we gonna do
if a spirit shows up?
It's fine! I'll be back by evening!
I'm heading out!
- Hurray!
- Wait, Miss Ayase!
Hurray!
Lady Momo! I have brought you
your sweet juice.
Huh?
Miss Ayase went to the hot springs district.
Seriously? I wanted to go with her!
Wanna play soccer?
You trap it, then...
Yup, that's it!
You're good!
Now try kicking it my way!
Get your pivot foot next to the ball, and
kick it here with the inside of your foot!
Oh, I'm sorry!
It's okay!
Here!
Sorry about that!
I'm so pathetic.
I'm glad Miss Ayase isn't here!
But if I practice here,
I might be able to show Miss Ayase
when the time is right!
Oh, that's amazing, Okarun!
You're so cool!
Hey, hey, Okarun!
Oh, sorry.
You in love with Momo?
Huh?
I hope they're getting along.
It's a first guy friend for Okarun,
so I'm sure I'd just get in the way.
Good for you, Okarun.
I mean, Momo is cute.
- For me, Miss Ayase was my first friend.
- Hey, pass!
I respect her, and she's very dear to me!
Nice pass!
I see, someone dear to you.
Someone you respect.
I really love Momo's face
and personality.
I do as well!
Huh?
You just said respect!
It's respect on top of all that!
Isn't that a bit unfair?
Then I'll add how I love
Momo's eyes! There, I win!
Wha...
Then I'll say all that, plus I love her mouth!
There! I win!
Nope, no good! That's no good!
You can't say "no good"!
I first started off saying I like her face,
so yours doesn't count!
Then your love of her eyes
won't count either!
It's fine!
I'm Momo's childhood friend!
There, I win!
Grrrr!
Win...
Huh? In what?
You can't just say
you win outta nowhere!
This is...
Right, I'm sorry.
What?
I'm starting to feel dizzy.
Time to head out.
It's too bad that it's an open-air bath,
but the walls are too high to see any scenery.
Oh, we already have someone here.
And she's quite a hottie!
What!?
You're so stubborn!
But I'll admit you've got some guts!
I'm not done yet! I haven't given up!
Hey, let's shake hands as friends!
Oh fine.
I got you now!
Damn you!
Miss Ayase would never be okay
with something this sneaky!
Admit defeat, Okarun!
No way! I'm not gonna give up!
Okarun!
Mr. Jiji, stop! Look at that!
Look at what?
That! Look!
Isn't it a bit strange there?
There wasn't a room
right next to the foyer, was there?
Young lady, you came
to a co-ed bath while being so young?
MALE/FEMALE COMMUNAL USE
WATCH YOUR FEET
There's no way I could read that!
Whew, so hot.
A beer would be nice right now!
Paradise!
I didn't notice at all, but you're right.
It was jutting out
when we look at it from the outside.
There should be something here.
It's hollow.
Yikes. What should I do?
I want to get out right now,
but those guys are in the way
so it's hard to get out.
Oh no! I have to hurry out of here.
I'm starting to feel lightheaded!
Let's try breaking it down.
Is it all right?
Probably not. We're renting the house,
but we gotta do it, right?
There has to be some reason...
A reason why my parents
ended up that way!
Young lady, do you know about gators?
Huh?
Gators? You mean those things
that look like lizards?
Nope, that's not it!
They're guys who often show up
in co-ed baths and target naked women.
Can I deal with all of them
using my psychic powers?
I've heard that a pack of wolves disperse
as soon as you strike their leader.
Crap!